[Music]
Hello, my name is Avdhoot Kamble ahi and majhi hi ji
gaadi hai hi magoon damage jhali hoti tar he
purna break out la ho tumpi e bumper
baghu sakta jo mage and ama jo iras hota to
shriram general insurance me aani ami
car services moon in Mundwa there ahi
repairing got done and purna bumper change jhala hota
so te home delivery service and Roon jar gadi get
you collected asel tari
thei services  You provide us with the help of
repairer wherever you go,
you can be totally
satisfied by the service, thank you sir, your
Shriram General Insurance is
out of five marks, you give it
five to five because of the reason I
called you and told them.  Next day
they would have provided car services,
collected the car for it and
within two days they had
provided all the documentation, so I am very thankful to them, I am very
thankful to General Insurance, Shriram
General Insurance and JATS Car Services,
also thank you
[Music]